Getting old might not be something that’s yet to cross your mind.
变老可能是你还未曾考虑过的事情。
But ageing is inevitably going to get the better of us one day, so it’s something I’m sure we’d all like control.
但衰老终有一天会降临到我们每个人身上，所以我相信这是我们都希望能掌控的事。
It would be great to have a long, healthy and happy life, and that’s why scientists are constantly seeking out evidence that will show us what we need to do to achieve longevity.
拥有漫长、健康且幸福的人生是件美好的事，这也是科学家们不断寻找证据，想要告诉我们如何才能实现长寿的原因。
We all know that regular exercise is good for us.
我们都知道规律运动对身体有益。
In recent years we’ve been told to aim to walk 10,000 steps a day to remain healthy, although other advice to do three brisk 10-minute walks a day is thought to be even more effective.
近年来，有人告诉我们每天要走10000步才能保持健康，不过也有建议称，每天进行三次10分钟的快走效果可能更好。
But the latest piece of research might put a spring in your step if you’re someone who walks at a fast pace.
但如果你本身走路速度较快，最新的一项研究可能会让你更加干劲十足。
That’s because, according to scientists, the speed at which people walk in their 40s is a sign of how much their brains, as well as their bodies, are ageing.
这是因为科学家们发现，人们在40多岁时的步行速度，能反映出他们的大脑和身体的衰老程度。
The BBC’s Philippa Roxby writes that tests on 1,000 people from New Zealand born in the 1970s found that slower walkers tended to show signs of "accelerated ageing".
英国广播公司的菲利帕·罗克斯比写道，对1000名出生于20世纪70年代的新西兰人进行的测试发现，走路较慢的人往往表现出“加速衰老”的迹象。
Their lungs, teeth and immune systems were in worse shape than those who walked faster.
他们的肺部、牙齿和免疫系统状况都比走路较快的人更差。
And to add insult to injury, the study found not only did slower walkers' bodies age more quickly, their faces looked older and they had smaller brains.
更糟糕的是，研究还发现，走路慢的人不仅身体衰老得更快，面容看起来也更显老，大脑也更小。
Professor Terrie E Moffitt, lead author of the study, told the BBC: "[it] found that a slow walk is a problem sign decades before old age."
该研究的主要作者特里·E·莫菲特教授向英国广播公司表示：“（研究）发现，走路慢是老年期到来前几十年就会出现的问题信号。”
This might be seen as a wake-up call for people with a slower gait who might feel it’s time to work out and get fitter.
这或许会给走路缓慢的人敲响警钟，让他们意识到是时候锻炼身体、增强体质了。
But it might be too late; researchers writing in JAMA Network Open say they were able to predict the walking speed of 45-year-olds using the results of intelligence, language and motor skills tests from when they were aged three.
但也许为时已晚：发表在《美国医学会网络开放期刊》上的研究称，研究人员通过分析人们三岁时的智力、语言和运动技能测试结果，就能预测他们45岁时的步行速度。
They also suggest that even in early life, there are signs showing which people will go on to have a healthier life.
研究人员还表示，即使在生命早期，就有迹象能表明哪些人未来会拥有更健康的人生。
So, what’s the point of knowing that a slower walking pace might mean a smaller brain?
那么，知道走路速度慢可能意味着大脑体积小，又有什么意义呢？
Well, researchers say measuring walking speed at a younger age, and understanding what this might mean, could be a way of testing treatments to slow human ageing.
研究人员表示，在年轻时测量步行速度，并了解其背后的含义，可能会成为测试延缓人类衰老疗法的一种方式。
This might help us make lifestyle changes while we’re still young and healthy.
这有助于我们在年轻健康的时候就做出生活方式上的改变。
Any steps we can take to prolong a good mental and physical state is a no brainer!
任何能帮助我们延长身心健康状态的措施，都是显而易见的明智之举！